icrossing.com 2006-02-07

# iCrossing, Inc. Privacy Statement - Legal

about us | management | organization | newsroom | careers | contacts  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
iCrossing, Inc. ("IC") respects the privacy concerns of the users of its Internet Sites ("Sites"), and has created this privacy statement to explain what information we gather from your visit to our Sites, and how such information may be used.

Use of Information

As a general policy no personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, or e-mail address, is automatically collected from your visit to IC Sites. However, certain non-personal information is recorded by the standard operation of IC's Internet servers. Information such as the type of browser being used, its operating system, and your IP address is gathered in order to enhance your online experience.

Our Sites' various registration forms and surveys may request that you give us contact information (such as your name, mailing and/or e-mail address) demographic information (such as your age and gender) and profile data (such as your preferences in web search). Information submitted at the time of registration or submission may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by IC and it's strategic business units, and may be shared with our Client partners. Personally identifiable information is never sold or leased to any third parties (including our clients and partners). With your permission, we may use your contact information to send you information about our company and what we are doing. You may always opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the Choice/Opt-out section below.

Our Sites use various order forms for you to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (such as your name, mailing and/or e-mail address), and when appropriate and necessary, financial information to process and/or your purchase of services from us.

IC may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with IC's rights or property, other IC web site users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

To the extent that any of our Sites accessible through the URL www.icrossinginc.com have additional or different practices or policies, these practices will be explained at that particular Site. 

Security

Security for all personally identifiable information is extremely important to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, IC cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

Use of Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's computer hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies make using our Sites easier by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you. These cookies are restricted for use only on our Sites, and do not transfer any personal information to any other party. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies; however, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. (Note: you will need to consult the help area of your browser application for instructions.) If you choose to disable your cookies setting or refuse to accept a cookie, some parts of IC's web sites will not function properly or may be considerably slower. For example, without cookies you will not be able to set personalized preferences.

Use of IP Addresses

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet provider whenever you're surfing the Web. When you requests pages from IC's Sites, our servers log your IP address. IC collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers and Clients, and to audit the use of our Site. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that your session will be logged, but you are anonymous to us. We may use your IP addresses in cooperation with your Internet provider to identify you if we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use or to protect our service, Sites, customers, clients, or others.

Links to Other Sites

IC is not responsible for the content or practices of third party websites that may be linked to our Sites. Our Sites may also be linked to websites operated by other companies. Visitors to these web sites should refer to each web site's respective privacy policies and practices.

Bulletin Boards and Chat Areas

Guests of IC's Sites are solely responsible for the content of messages they post on public forums, such as chat rooms and bulletin boards. Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personal information (e.g., user name, e-mail address, phone number) on the bulletin boards or in the chat areas, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other people. 

Choice/Opt-Out

Our Sites may provide you the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us at the point where we request information about you. You always have the option of removing your name from any e-mail list to not receive future communications. In order to ensure immediate removal from any list, it is best to follow the specific instructions outlined within the communications you receive from us since IC operates several sites tailored to specific interests. However, if you are unable to complete the process indicated in the communications, then just send us an e-mail with a copy of the undesired email attached to the request and state you wish to be removed from the mailing list.

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our Sites, or your dealings with our Sites, you can contact: 

  * iCrossing, Inc., 14822 North 73rd Street, Scottsdale AZ 85260, Attention: Legal Department

Information provided by you via general e-mail inquiries to IC such as your e-mail address is used only to respond to your inquiries in the ordinary course of business, and is never shared with third parties. To view educational material on consumer privacy, please see <http://www.ftc.gov/>

Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using IC's, you signify your acceptance of the IC Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Sites. IC reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time, so visitors are encouraged to review this policy from time to time. Your continued use of the IC Sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

_(Last updated January 20, 2006)_

©2006 iCrossing, Inc®. All Rights Reserved.  
Do not duplicate or redistribute in any form
